Preliminary Guide to the Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records, 1952-2000 MS2083
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Larry King show, 1970-ca. 1990; Series 5; 112 Linear Feet
  - Larry King and Jim Bohannon show program logs, 1979-1997; Series 5 Subseries 2; 3 Linear Feet
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, June 10, 1993-September 15, 1993; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, September 16, 1993- December 27, 1993; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, December 28, 1993-April 30, 1994; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, May 2, 1994-August 23, 1994; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, August 24, 1994-December 30, 1994; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report & Week-in-Review, January 2, 1995-April 19, 1995; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report & Week-in-Review, April 20, 1995-July 17, 1995; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report & Week-in-Review, July 20, 1995-September 23, 1995; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, July 2, 1996-September 30, 1996; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, October 1, 1996-December 30, 1996; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, January 1, 1997-February 13, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, February 14, 1997-May 25, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, May 16, 1997-December 4, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - JBS, Larry King, Mutual Signed Release Forms [1/2], 1993; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - JBS, Larry King, Mutual Signed Release Forms [2/2], 1994-1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - JBS List of Guests, 1989-1992; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - JBS Signed Release Forms [1/3], 1995-1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - JBS Signed Release Forms [2/3], 1995-1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - JBS Signed Release Forms [3/3], 1995-1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Larry King Show- Release Statements, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folders 1-2)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest Permissions, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folders 3-4)
  - Larry King show audiotapes, 1978-1999; Series 5 Subseries 3; 97.5 Linear Feet 65 cartons
    Tapes of the Jim Bohannon Show were previously included in some of the containers. This subseries has since been reorganized to include only Larry King Show tapes.
    - January 1978 - September 1981, 1978-1981 (Carton 1)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Jan. 1978 - Oct. 1980 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1980 - Mar. 1981 Audio Contents Box #3: Mar. 1981 - Sept. 1981
    - October 1981 - May 1983, 1981-1983 (Carton 2)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Oct. 1981 - Feb. 1982 Audio Contents Box #2: Mar. 1982 - Aug. 1982 Audio Contents Box #3: Aug. 1982 - May 1983
    - May 1983 - February 1984, 1983-1984 (Carton 3)
      Audio Contents Box #1: May 1983 - Oct. 1983 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1983 - Feb. 1984 Audio Contents Box #3: Feb. 1984
    - February 1984 - May 1984 (Carton 4)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Feb. 1984 - Mar. 1984 Audio Contents Box #2: Mar. 1984 - Apr. 1984 Audio Contents Box #3: Apr. 1984 - May 1984
    - June 1984 - December 1984 (Carton 5)
      Audio Contents Box #1: June 1984 - Sept. 1984 Audio Contents Box #2: Sept. 1984 - Oct. 1984 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1984 - Dec. 1984
    - January 1985 - April 1985 (Carton 6)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Jan. 1985 - Feb. 1985 Audio Contents Box #2: Feb. 1985 - Mar. 1985 Audio Contents Box #3: Mar. 1985 - Apr. 1985
    - May 1985 - July 1985 (Carton 7)
      Audio Contents Box #1: May 1985 - June 1985 Audio Contents Box #2: June 1985 - July 1985 Audio Contents Box #3: July 1985
    - August 1985 - October 1985 (Carton 8)
      Audio Contents Box #1: August 1985 Audio Contents Box #2: August 1985 - September 1985 Audio Contents Box #3: September 1985 - October 1985
    - October 1985 - December 1985 (Carton 9)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Oct. 1985 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1985 - Nov. 1985 Audio Contents Box #3: Nov. 1985 - Dec. 1985
    - December 1985 - February 1986, 1985-1986 (Carton 10)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Dec. 1985 - Jan. 1986 Audio Contents Box #2: Jan. 1986 Audio Contents Box #3: Feb. 1986
    - February 1986 - April 1986 (Carton 11)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Feb. 1986 - Mar. 1986 Audio Contents Box #2: Mar. 1986 - Apr. 1986 Audio Contents Box #3: Apr. 1986
    - April 1986 - July 1986 (Carton 12)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Apr. 1986 - May 1986 Audio Contents Box #2: May 1986 - June 1986 Audio Contents Box #3: June 1986 - July 1986
    - July 1986 - September 1986 (Carton 13)
      Audio Contents Box #1: July 1986 Audio Contents Box #2: July 1986 - Aug. 1986 Audio Contents Box #3: Aug. 1986 - Sept. 1986
    - September 1986 - November 1986 (Carton 14)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Sept. 1986 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1986 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1986 - Nov. 1986
    - November 1986 - January 1987, 1986-1987 (Carton 15)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Nov. 1986 Audio Contents Box #2: Dec. 1986 Audio Contents Box #3: Dec. 1986 - Jan. 1987
    - January 1987 - March 1987 (Carton 16)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Jan. 1987 - Feb. 1987 Audio Contents Box #2: Feb. 1987 Audio Contents Box #3: Feb. 1987 - Mar. 1987
    - March 1987 - May 1987 (Carton 17)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Mar. 1987 - Apr. 1987 Audio Contents Box #2: Apr. 1987 Audio Contents Box #3: Apr. 1987 - May 1987
    - May 1987 - June 1987 (Carton 18)
      Audio Contents Box #1: May 1987 Audio Contents Box #2: May 1987 - June 1987 Audio Contents Box #3: June 1987
    - June 1987 - August 1987 (Carton 19)
      Audio Contents Box #1: June 1987 - July 1987 Audio Contents Box #2: July 1987 Audio Contents Box #3: July 1987 - August 1987
    - August 1987 - September 1987 (Carton 20)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Aug. 1987 Audio Contents Box #2: Aug. 1987 - Sept. 1987 Audio Contents Box #3: Sept. 1987
    - September 1987 - November 1987 (Carton 21)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Sept. 1987 - Oct. 1987 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1987 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1987 - Nov. 1987
    - November 1987 - January 1988, 1987-1988 (Carton 22)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Nov. 1987 Audio Contents Box #2: Nov. 1987 - Dec. 1987 Audio Contents Box #3: Dec. 1987 - Jan. 1988
    - January 1988 - April 1988 (Carton 23)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Jan. 1988 - Feb. 1988 Audio Contents Box #2: Feb. 1988 - Mar. 1988 Audio Contents Box #3: Mar. 1988 - Apr. 1988
    - April 1988 - June 1988 (Carton 24)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Apr. 1988 - May 1988 Audio Contents Box #2: May 1988 Audio Contents Box #3: May 1988 - June 1988
    - June 1988 - August 1988 (Carton 25)
      Audio Contents Box #1: June 1988 - July 1988 Audio Contents Box #2: July 1988 - Aug. 1988 Audio Contents Box #3: Aug. 1988
    - August 1988 - November 1988 (Carton 26)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Aug. 1988 - Sept. 1988 Audio Contents Box #2: Sept. 1988 - Oct. 1988 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1988 - Nov. 1988
    - November 1988 - February 1989, 1988-1989 (Carton 27)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Nov. 1988 - Dec. 1988 Audio Contents Box #2: Dec. 1988 - Jan. 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: Jan. 1989 - Feb. 1989
    - February 1989 - April 1989 (Carton 28)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Feb. 1989 - Mar. 1989 Audio Contents Box #2: Mar. 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: Mar. 1989 - Apr. 1989
    - April 1989 - May 1989 (Carton 29)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Apr. 1989 Audio Contents Box #2: Apr. 1989 - May 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: May 1989
    - May 1989 - July 1989 (Carton 30)
      Audio Contents Box #1: May 1989 - June 1989 Audio Contents Box #2: June 1989 - July 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: July 1989
    - July 1989 - September 1989 (Carton 31)
      Audio Contents Box #1: July 1989 Audio Contents Box #2: July 1989 - Aug. 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: Aug. 1989 - Sept. 1989
    - September 1989 - October 1989 (Carton 32)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Sept. 1989 Audio Contents Box #2: Sept. 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: Sept. 1989 - Oct. 1989
    - October 1989 - November 1989 (Carton 33)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Oct. 1989 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1989 - Nov. 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: Nov. 1989
    - November 1989 - January 1990, 1989-1990 (Carton 34)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Nov. 1989 - Dec. 1989 Audio Contents Box #2: Dec. 1989 Audio Contents Box #3: Dec. 1989 - Jan. 1990
    - January 1990 - February 1990 (Carton 35)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Jan. 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: Jan. 1990 - Feb. 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: Feb. 1990
    - February 1990 - April 1990 (Carton 36)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Feb. 1990 - Mar. 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: Mar. 1990 - Apr. 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: Apr. 1990
    - April 1990 - May 1990 (Carton 37)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Apr. 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: May 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: May 1990
    - May 1990 - June 1990 (Carton 38)
      Audio Contents Box #1: May 1990 - June 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: June 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: June 1990
    - July 1990 - August 1990 (Carton 39)
      Audio Contents Box #1: July 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: July 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: July 1990 - Aug. 1990
    - August 1990 - September 1990 (Carton 40)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Aug. 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: Aug. 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: Aug. 1990 - Sept. 1990
    - September 1990 - October 1990 (Carton 41)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Sept. 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: Sept. 1990 - Oct. 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1990
    - October 1990 - November 1990 (Carton 42)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Oct. 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1990 - Nov. 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: Nov. 1990
    - November 1990 - December 1990 (Carton 43)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Nov. 1990 - Dec. 1990 Audio Contents Box #2: Dec. 1990 Audio Contents Box #3: Dec. 1990
    - December 1990 - February 1991, 1990-1991 (Carton 44)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Dec. 1990 - Jan. 1991 Audio Contents Box #2: Jan. 1991 Audio Contents Box #3: Jan. 1991 - Feb. 1991
    - February 1991 - March 1991 (Carton 45)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Feb. 1991 Audio Contents Box #2: Feb. 1991 - Mar. 1991 Audio Contents Box #3: Mar. 1991
    - March 1991 - May 1991 (Carton 46)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Mar. 1991 - Apr. 1991 Audio Contents Box #2: Apr. 1991 Audio Contents Box #3: Apr. 1991 - May 1991
    - May 1991 - July 1991 (Carton 47)
      Audio Contents Box #1: May 1991 - June 1991 Audio Contents Box #2: June 1991 - July 1991 Audio Contents Box #3: July 1991
    - July 1991 - September 1991 (Carton 48)
      Audio Contents Box #1: July 1991 - Aug. 1991 Audio Contents Box #2: Aug. 1991 Audio Contents Box #3: Aug. 1991 - Sept. 1991
    - September 1991 - October 1991 (Carton 49)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Sept. 1991 Audio Contents Box #2: Sept. 1991 - Oct. 1991 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1991
    - October 1991 - December 1991 (Carton 50)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Oct. 1991 - Nov. 1991 Audio Contents Box #2: Nov. 1991 Audio Contents Box #3: Nov. 1991 - Dec. 1991
    - December 1991 - February 1992, 1991-1992 (Carton 51)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Dec. 1991 - Jan. 1992 Audio Contents Box #2: Jan. 1992 Audio Contents Box #3: Jan. 1992 - Feb. 1992
    - February 1992 - April 1992 (Carton 52)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Feb. 1992 - Mar. 1992 Audio Contents Box #2: Mar. 1992 Audio Contents Box #3: Mar. 1992 - Apr. 1992
    - April 1992 - July 1992 (Carton 53)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Apr. 1992 - May 1992 Audio Contents Box #2: May 1992 - June 1992 Audio Contents Box #3: June 1992 - July 1992
    - July 1992 - August 1992 (Carton 54)
      Audio Contents Box #1: July 1992 Audio Contents Box #2: July 1992 - Aug. 1992 Audio Contents Box #3: Aug. 1992
    - August 1992 - November 1992 (Carton 55)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Aug. 1992 - Sept. 1992 Audio Contents Box #2: Sept. 1992 - Oct. 1992 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1992 - Nov. 1992
    - November 1992 - December 1992 (Carton 56)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Nov. 1992 Audio Contents Box #2: Nov. 1992 - Dec. 1992 Audio Contents Box #3: Dec. 1992
    - December 1992 - April 1993, 1992-1993 (Carton 57)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Dec. 1992 - Jan. 1993 Audio Contents Box #2: Jan. 1993 - Feb. 1993 Audio Contents Box #3: Feb. 1993 - Apr. 1993
    - April 1993 - July 1993 (Carton 58)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Apr. 1993 - May 1993 Audio Contents Box #2: May 1993 - June 1993 Audio Contents Box #3: July 1993
    - July 1993 - September 1993 (Carton 59)
      Audio Contents Box #1: July 1993 - Aug. 1993 Audio Contents Box #2: Aug. 1993 - Sept. 1993 Audio Contents Box #3: Sept. 1993
    - September 1993 - November 1993 (Carton 60)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Sept. 1993 - Oct. 1993 Audio Contents Box #2: Oct. 1993 Audio Contents Box #3: Oct. 1993 - Nov. 1993
    - November 1993 - December 1993 (Carton 61)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Nov. 1993 Audio Contents Box #2: Nov. 1993 - Dec. 1993 Audio Contents Box #3: Dec. 1993
    - December 1993 - January 1994, 1993-1994 (Carton 62)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Dec. 1993 Audio Contents Box #2: Dec. 1993 - Jan. 1994 Audio Contents Box #3: Jan. 1994
    - January 1994 - March 1994 (Carton 63)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Jan. 1994 - Feb. 1994 Audio Contents Box #2: Feb. 1994 Audio Contents Box #3: Feb. 1994 - Mar. 1994
    - March 1994 - April 1994 (Carton 64)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Mar. 1994 Audio Contents Box #2: Mar. 1994 - Apr. 1994 Audio Contents Box #3: Apr. 1994
    - April 1994 - December 1999, 1994-1999 (Carton 65)
      Audio Contents Box #1: Apr. 1994 - May 1994 Audio Contents Box #2: May 1994 Audio Contents Box #3: May 1994 Audio Contents Box #4: May 1994 - Dec. 1999 (includes misc. tapes and 2 videocassettes)
- Mike Walker show, 1990-1995; Series 6
  - 1994 (Carton 1)
  - 1994 - 1995 (Carton 2)
  - 1994 (Carton 3)
  - ca. 1990 - ca. 1995 (Carton 4)
  - ca. 1990 - ca. 1995 (Carton 5)
    Includes audiocassettes from the Jim Bohannon show.
    Bohannon, Jim
  - 1994 (Carton 6)
- Mutual Broadcasting series, 1980-1999; Series 7
  - Dick Clark's National Music Survey, ca. 1980 - ca. 1999; 30 Linear Feet 20 cartons
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 1)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 2)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 3)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 4)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 5)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 6)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 7)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 8)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 9)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 10)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 11)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 12)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 13)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 14)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 15)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 16)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 17)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 18)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 19)
    - Tape masters, undated (Carton 20)
  - American Country specials, undated
    - American Country specials tape masters, undated (Carton 21)
    - American Country specials tape masters, undated (Carton 22)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 23)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 24)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 25)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 26)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 27)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 28)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 29)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 30)
    - American Country specials and Christmas specials, undated (Carton 31)
    - American Country specials and Christmas specials, undated (Carton 32)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 33)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 34)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 35)
    - American Country specials, undated (Carton 36)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 39)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 40)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 41)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 42)
    - Country takes Manhattan, 1993 (Carton 43)
    - Country takes Manhattan, 1993 May (Carton 44)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 49)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 50)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 51)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 54)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 55)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 56)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 57)
    - American Country special, undated (Carton 58)
    - American Country special, undated (Carton 59)
    - Country special rebo. Christmas: Kenny [Rogers?], [Dull?], and Willy [Nelson?], undated (Carton 60)
    - Country special Reba [MacIntyre?] Christmas, undated (Carton 61)
    - Country special Mandrell Christmas, 1980 (Carton 62)
    - Country special Mandrell Christmas, 1980 (Carton 63)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 64)
    - Country special, undated (Carton 65)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 68)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 69)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 70)
    - Country specials, undated (Carton 71)
    - Country specials, undated (Carton 72)
    - Country specials, undated (Carton 73)
    - Country specials, undated (Carton 74)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 75)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 76)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 77)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 78)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 79)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 80)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 81)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 82)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 83)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 84)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 85)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 86)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 87)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 88)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 89)
    - American Country country comments, undated (Carton 90)
  - Listen in, undated
    - Listen in w/ tapes, undated (Carton 45)
    - Listen in w/ tapes, undated (Carton 46)
    - Listen in w/ tapes, undated (Carton 47)
    - Listen in w/ tapes, undated (Carton 48)
  - Rock special, 1990
    - Rock special, 1990 (Carton 37)
    - Rock special, 1990 (Carton 38)
  - Pop, undated
    - Fantest Pop, 1994 May - July (Carton 53)
  - Like only yesterday - Rock - TNT, undated
    - Like only yesterday - Rock - TNT, undated (Carton 66)
    - Like only yesterday - Rock - TNT, undated (Carton 67)
  - LFG, undated
- America in the morning, 1984-2000; Series 8; 48 Linear Feet 32 cartons
  - 1984 September - December (Carton 1)
  - 1985 January - May (Carton 2)
  - 1985 July - November 3 (Carton 3)
  - 1985 December - 1986 March (Carton 4)
  - 1986 April - August (Carton 5)
  - 1986 September - December (Carton 6)
  - 1987 January - April (Carton 7)
  - 1987 May - August (Carton 8)
  - 1987 September - December (Carton 9)
  - 1982 January - June (Carton 10)
  - 1983 July - 1984 February (Carton 11)
  - 1984 March - December (Carton 12)
  - 1988 December - 1990 June (Carton 13)
  - 1990 May - August (Carton 14)
  - 1990 November - 1991 April (Carton 15)
  - 1991 May - October (Carton 16)
  - 1991 November - 1992 April (Carton 17)
  - 1992 MAy - October (Carton 18)
  - 1992 November - 1993 June (Carton 19)
  - 1993 June - December (Carton 20)
  - 1994 January - July (Carton 21)
  - 1994 September - December (Carton 22)
  - 1995 January - August (Carton 23)
  - 1996 March - June, 1996 September - October (Carton 24)
  - 1996 November - 1997 October (Carton 25)
  - 1997 - 1998 (Carton 26)
  - 1998 January - March, 1998 July - August, 1998 November - December (Carton 27)
  - 1999 March - April, 1999 July - August, 2000 January - February (Carton 28)
  - 2000 July - December (Carton 29)
  - 1997 July - August, 1997 November - December, 1999 November - December (Carton 30)
  - 1995 September - December (Carton 31)
  - 1999 May - June, 1999 September - October, 2000 March - June (Carton 32)
- NBC extra, 1980-1998; Series 9
  - 1980-1989, audiotapes (Carton 1)
  - 1987-1988, audiotapes (Carton 2)
  - 1988 - 1990, audiotapes (Carton 3)
  - 1991, audiotapes (Carton 4)
  - 1992 - 1993, audiotapes (Carton 5)
  - 1994 - 1996, audiotapes (Carton 6)
  - 1997 - 1998, audiotapes (Carton 7)
- NBC sound bites, undated; Series 10
  - T985-T1013 (Carton 1)
  - T1014-T1048 (Carton 2)
- Newsbreakers, 1985-1990; Series 11
  - 1985 - 1988, audiotapes (Carton 1)
  - 1986 - 1989, audiotapes (Carton 2)
  - 1988 June 19 - 1989 February 19, audiotapes (Carton 3)
  - 1989 February 26 - October 15, audiotapes (Carton 4)
  - 1986 May 17 - 1987 January 18, audiotapes (Carton 5)
  - 1987 February 8 - October 4, audiotapes (Carton 6)
  - 1987 October 11 - 1988 June 12, audiotapes (Carton 7)
- Reporter roundup, 1976-1988; Series 12
  - 1980 July 1 - 1981 May 16 (Carton 1, Flat box 1)
  - 1981 May 23 - 1982 April 3 (Carton 1, Flat box 2)
  - 1976 April - 1988 December, audiotapes (Carton 2)
  - 1986 - 1988, audiotapes (Carton 3)
  - 1983 - 1985, audiotapes (Carton 4)
- Seems like yesterday, 1987-1989; Series 13; 4.5 Linear Feet 3 cartons
  Audiocassettes.
  - 1987 October - 1988 June (Carton 1)
  - 1989 February - June (Carton 2)
  - 1988 December - 1989 October (Carton 3)
- The week in review, 1984-2000; Series 14
  - The week in review scripts, 1984-1996
    Scripts from radio shows.
    - 1984 - 1986 (Carton 1)
    - 1990 - 1991 (Carton 2)
    - 1987 - 1991 (Carton 3)
    - 1993 - 1996 (Carton 4)
  - The week in review audiotapes, 1983-1992; 4.5 Linear Feet 2 cartons
    - 1983-1987 (Carton 1)
    - 1986-1988 (Carton 2)
    - 1990-1992 (Carton 3)
  - The week in review audiotapes, 1984-2000
    - 1996 September 12 - 1997 March 28 (Carton 1)
    - 1997 April 4 - December 12 (Carton 2)
    - 1997 December - 1998 August 28 (Carton 3)
    - 1998 September 4 - 1999 May 2 (Carton 4)
    - 1999 February 8 - 2000 August 8 (Carton 5)
    - 1995 November 3 - 1996 July 5 (Carton 6)
    - 2000 February 4 - October 20 (Carton 7)
    - 1996 February 23 - October 26 (Carton 8)
    - 1990 November 29 - 1991 July 17 (Carton 9)
    - 1991 July 30 - 1992 April 3 (Carton 10)
    - 1992 April 10 - December 17 (Carton 11)
    - 1993 January 1 - September 3 (Carton 12)
    - 1993 September 10 - 1994 May 27 (Carton 13)
    - 1994 June 3 - 1995 February 17 (Carton 14)
    - 1985 September 27 - 1986 June 27 (Carton 15)
    - 1984 December 14 - 1985 September 20 (Carton 16)
    - 1987 March 20 - November 27 (Carton 17)
    - 1995 February 24 - October 27 (Carton 18)
    - 1986 July 4 - 1987 March 13 (Carton 19)
    - 1987 December 4 - 1988 August 26 (Carton 20)
    - 1988 September 2 - 1989 May 26 (Carton 21)
    - 1989 June 2 - 1990 February 16 (Carton 22)
- Weekend headliners, 1987-1999; Series 15; 21 Linear Feet 14 cartons
  - 1989 - 1996, audiocassettes (Carton 1)
  - 1995 June - 1996 March, audiocassettes (Carton 2)
  - 1994 October - 1995 June, audiocassettes (Carton 3)
  - 1991 September - 1994 August, audiocassettes (Carton 4)
  - 1989 - 1991 August, audiocassettes (Carton 5)